https://bahai.soc.srcf.net/about/privacy-notice/

Skip to content
How we use your personal information – Cambridge University Bahá’í Society (CUBS)
This statement explains how the Cambridge University Bahá’í Society (“we”, “us” and “our”) handles and uses the personal information we collect about our members for processes relating to our operations and activities.
When changes are made to this statement, we will publish the updated version on our website.
The controller for your personal information is the Cambridge University Bahá’í Society. The person responsible for data protection within our society is the Secretary who can be contacted at bahai [at] cusu.cam.ac.uk.
How we use your personal information
We collect and process your personal information for a number of purposes, including:
Maintaining your personal details (e.g. your name and preferred contact details), including ensuring effective communications with you.
Keeping financial records (e.g. payment for reimbursement of our society expenses).
Maintaining a formal record of your activities with us.
Undertaking research into our activities.
Managing complaints made to us.
Managing society alumni relations and fundraising.
Our normal legal basis for processing your personal information is that we believe it is in our legitimate interests to do so, in order for the society to run effectively and efficiently, and as we only collect and use minimal information for the limited purposes listed here we do not consider that your own interests override ours.  If we use your personal information outside of the purposes listed here, we will seek your consent to do so in advance.
We keep your personal information for as long as we need it, and usually for three years after your membership ceases.
How we share your personal information
Personal information is not shared outside of the society and its members.
We use University IT facilities to store electronic copies of personal information.
We may also be subject to a legal requirement (with or without your consent) to share your personal information with the University or a government agency (such as the police or security services or other statutory authorities with investigatory powers) under special circumstances (e.g. relating to tax, crime or health and safety).  Where feasible and appropriate, we will notify you of our intention to share such information in advance.
Your rights
You have the right to access the personal information that we hold about you. You also have the right to ask us to correct any inaccurate personal information we hold about you, to delete personal information, or otherwise restrict our processing, or to object to processing or communications, or to receive an electronic copy of the personal information you provided to us. Please note that all of these rights are qualified in various ways.
If you have questions or concerns about how your personal information is used, please contact us using the above details.
If you remain unhappy with the way your information is being handled, or with the response received from us, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office at Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, SK9 5AF (https://ico.org.uk/).
Last updated: 16 May 2018
Primary Sidebar Widget Area
Contact We are a registered society at the University of Cambridge in the UK. Are you a current student or staff member and want to learn more about the Bahá’í Faith? Email us at bahai [at] cusu.cam.ac.uk. We’re always happy to meet new people!
Bahá'í Links
CU Baha'i Society Facebook Page
CU Baha'i Society Mailing List
Cambridge Bahá'í Community Facebook Page
Cambridge Bahá'í Community Website
UK Bahá'ís Website
Worldwide Bahá'í Community Website
Recent Posts
Devotionals (2)
Festival of Ideas (18)
Firesides (16)
Holy Days (7)
Soul Food (10)
Study Circles (1)
Talks (31)
Uncategorized (6)
Archives
November 2020 (1)
November 2019 (1)
October 2019 (1)
September 2019 (1)
January 2019 (1)
October 2018 (2)
November 2017 (1)
September 2017 (1)
September 2016 (1)
February 2015 (1)
October 2014 (1)
September 2014 (6)
April 2014 (1)
February 2014 (1)
January 2014 (3)
November 2013 (3)
October 2013 (2)
September 2013 (3)
August 2013 (1)
July 2013 (1)
June 2013 (3)
May 2013 (3)
April 2013 (3)
March 2013 (4)
February 2013 (3)
January 2013 (3)
October 2012 (3)
November 2011 (1)
October 2011 (2)
May 2010 (1)
November 2009 (2)
October 2009 (1)
February 2009 (1)
November 2008 (1)
Scroll Up
